Rubius and auron have remembered the controversy
Rubius y auron han recordado la polémica
from last year about Mexico, pointing
del año pasado sobre México señalándose
each other out as responsible for the
mutuamente como responsables de los
comments that generated the funa. I don't know
comentarios que generaron la funa no sé
why every time I play something with auron
por qué cada vez que juego con auron
on Stream it always ends up
algo en Stream siempre acabo vamos acaba
being the third world war on
siendo la tercera guerra mundial en
Twitter. Oh my goodness it's
Twitter madre mía Menos mal que son
faces just getting gun shots
caritas acab recibiendo fotos de pistola
at me. Focus invited me a month ago to
a m Focus me invitó hace hace un mes a
play deol yas in this second part
jugar deol yas en esta segunda parte
Rubius jokes about the comments
Rubius bromea sobre los comentarios de
Unleashing laughter among the participants
Desatando risas entre los participantes
while the topic continues to generate
mientras el tema sigue generando
controversy it was incredible I didn't expect it
polémica fue increble no me lo esperaba
but what happened what did you say to get
pero qué pasó que dijiste para que se
funa nothing nothing The truth is you don't have
funar nada nada La verad pas no tenéis
balls that's what happens auron said
huevos eso es lo que pasa que auron dijo
that Mexico was [ __ ] and that he
que México era una [__] y que lo
hated it I only said that it was
odiaba yo solo dije que estaba
far away How to say say that auron said
lejos Cómo decir decir que auron dijo
that Mexico hated Mexico and
que México odiaba México y
that mico I
que mico
said that Mexico was a bit far away for me
dije que México me pillaba un poco lejos
but that I would love to go but the thing is that
pero que me encantaría ir pero es que
auron went too far I said that
auron se pasó tres pueblos dije que iba
Luisito was going to go and he said I don't know what
a ir Luisito y él dijo No sé qué una
[ __ ] I don't know what no no no no no what about the
[__] no sé qué no no no no no lo de la
[ __ ] you said it I remember it like it
[__] lo dijiste tú lo recuerdo como si
was yesterday finally both streamers
fuera ayer finalmente ambos streamers
reflect in a humorous way on
reflexionan de forma humorística sobre
how the controversy broke out making it clear
cómo se desató la polémica dejando Claro
that it was all a
que todo fue un
misunderstanding well it was nothing it's
malentendido bueno es que fue ha nada ya
been two years and today today history repeats itself I
pasado dos años y hoy hoy se repite la
say what if it were up to us Chile would
digo qué si por noi fuera chile
disappear you know so imagine
desaparecería Sabes Así que imagínate
man what what are you saying why
tío qué qué dices por qué
Chile then they call me man [ __ ]
chile yo luego me dicen tío huevón
and [ __ ] and rocked
culado y concha de tu madre y mecido
because you are man
porque lo eres tío